<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<!--Can store information regarding, text images, links-->

<PageModel id ="FamilySupport-ParentResources">


  <TextList>

    <Text id="P1">
      Child Cancer Foundation aims to provide up-to-date information for families. Below is a list of websites providing additional information, research documents and details about child cancer from around the world.
    </Text>
    <Text>
      Kidscope
      www.kidscope.org
      An organization which has been formed to help families and children better understand the effects of cancer and chemotherapy.

      CancerCare, Inc.
      www.cancercareinc.org

      Chemo Kids
      http://www.chemo4kids.com/cancer-resources/
      This site offers simplified information about chemotherapy and its use to treat cancer.

      Candlelighters
      www.candlelighters.org/
      The Candlelighters mission is to educate, support, serve, and advocate for families of children with cancer, survivors of childhood cancer and professionals who care for them.

      ACT
      www.act.org.uk
      The site of the Association for Children with life-threatening or terminal conditions and their families. This site is in the process of redevelopment and will include access to a web-based research journal called LitpaedpalLit.

      International Confederation of Child Cancer Parent Organisations
      www.icccpo.org

      Action for Children and Youth in Aotearoa
      www.acya.org.nz
      This site has many excellent documents relating to areas of rights of children and youth.

      Starbright
      www.starbrightworld.org
      Starbright World is an online social network where teens (ages 13 to 20) who have serious medical conditions, and siblings of seriously ill teens, can connect with each other via moderated chat rooms, games, bulletin boards, videos, and more.

      CancerBACKUP
      www.cancerbackup.org.uk
      Contains very useful information.

      Children's Cancer Fund of New York Medical College
      www.childrenscancerfund.org
      The site of the Children's Cancer Fund of New York Medical College, led by Dr. S. Jayabose, Chief of Pediatric Hematology-Oncology at New York Medical College.
    </Text>
  </TextList>


  <ImageList>
    <Image id="Bottom">images/MotherandChild.png</Image>
  </ImageList>

  <LinksList>
  </LinksList>



</PageModel>